A Guide to the Harry Downing Temple. Jr., Papers, 1872-2004
Special Collections and University Archives, Virginia Tech
- Series VI: Research Files for Future Bugle's Echo, 1934-2004 (bulk, 1934-1989)
  - Research Files, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Research Files, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Research Files, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Research Files, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Research Files (2 folders), 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 10-11)
  - Research Files (2 folders), 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 12-13)
  - Research Files, 1976-1978 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Research Files, 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Research Files, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Research Files, 1980-1989 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Research Files, 1947-2004 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - "Athletics Statistics of VPI 1872-1951", 1951 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Senate Notes, 1958-1966 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Series VII: Photographs and Images for The Bugle's Echo, pre-1872-1920
  - Photographs, Volume 1, Chapters 1-21, pre-1872 to 1892 (Box 1P, Folder 1-21)
  - Photographs, Volume 1, Chapters 22-27, 1892-1898 (Box 2P, Folder 1-6)
  - Photographs, Volume 1, Chapters 28-30, 1889-1900 (Box 3P, Folder 1-3)
  - Photographs, Volume 2, Chapters 31-36; negatives of color plates from volumes 1 and 2, 1900-1906 (Box 4P, Folder 1-8)
  - Photographs, Volume 2, Chapters 37-38, 1906-1908 (Box 5P, Folder 1-4)
  - Photographs, Volume 2, Chapters 39-42, 1908-1912 (Box 6P, Folder 1-5)
  - Photographs, Volume 3, Chapters 43-45, 1912-1915 (Box 7P, Folder 1-4)
  - Photographs, Volume 3, Chapters 45-47, 1914-1917 (Box 8P, Folder 1-6)
  - Photographs, Volume 3, Chapters 48-50, 1917-1920 (Box 9P, Folder 1-6)
  - Photographs, Volume 4, Chapter 56, 1925-1926 (Box 15P, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, Volume 4, Chapter 57, 1926-1927 (Box 15P, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, Volume 4, Chapter 58, 1927-1928 (Box 15P, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, Volume 4, Chapter 59, 1928-1929 (Box 15P, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, Volume 4, Chapter 60, 1929-1930 (Box 15P, Folder 5)
  - Duplicate photographs, Chapters 2-3, 48, 50 (Box 10P, Folder 1-5)
  - Photographs (by chapter): Chapters 2-5, 51, 61-64 (Box 12P, Folder 12-20)
  - Photographs (by decade): 1800s, 1900s-1960s, undated (Box 12P, Folder 2-11)
  - Duplicate photographs (by decade), 1890s-1970s (Box 11P, Folder 1-10)
  - Photographs (by topic)
    - Athletics (Box 14P, Folder 1)
    - Blacksburg (Box 14P, Folder 2)
    - Campus buildings and views (Box 14P, Folder 3)
    - Candids/Campus life (Box 14P, Folder 4)
    - Corps of Cadets and Military life (Box 14P, Folder 5)
    - Military (Box 12P, Folder 1)
    - Montgomery County (Box 14P, Folder 6)
    - People (identified by name) (Box 14P, Folder 7)
    - ROTC camp (Box 14P, Folder 8)
    - Student activities (Box 14P, Folder 9)
    - Trains (Box 14P, Folder 10)
    - Southwest Virginia (Box 14P, Folder 12)
    - War Memorial Chapel (Box 14P, Folder 11)
  - Color plates and negatives, book jackets (Box 13P)
  - Negatives and slides, n.d. (Box 15P, Folder 6)
  - Print of 1896 Uniforms, n.d. (Folder 1)
  - Prints and negatives from illustrations used in The Bugle's Echo volumes (Folder 3, Box 33)
  - Slides of Bugles Echo photographs, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Scrapbook pages, 1934-1938 (Box 15P, Folder 7)